A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Commissioner of the Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1984-1994, 2004-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1984-1994, 2006.
  - 1984-1993 (bulk 1990-1993) (Accession 36853)., 58 cu. ft. (58 boxes)
    - Farmers Market Network, Virginia - Operations and Plans, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Food and Beverage Expo, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Food and Dairy Administration, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Friends of the Industry of Agriculture, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Gainsharing, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Gasoline - oxygenated, 1993. (Box 31)
    - General Assembly - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 31)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Governmental Employees Association, Virginia, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Governor's Office, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Governor Wilder - Accomplishments (1990-1992), 1993. (Box 31)
    - Groundwater Protection Steering Committee, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Harrisonburg Laboratory, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Health, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Horse Center, Virginia, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Horse Council, Virginia, 1993. (Box 31)
    - House of Representatives, U.S., 1993. (Box 31)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Incentive Pay Plan, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Incentive Fund and Employee Productivity, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Information Management, Council on, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Indirect Cost Recovery, 1993. (Box 31)
    - State Internal Auditor, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Issues - Critical, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Kellogg, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1993. (Box 31)
    - Legislation (for 1994), 1993. (Box 31)
    - Legislation, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Legislative Studies (VDACS), 1993-1994. (Box 31)
    - Liaison Office, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Mandates by Executive Agencies, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Market Promotion Program (MPP), 1993. (Box 31)
    - Media Policy, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum of Agreement - VDACS/Virginia State University, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum of Agreement - Dairy and Foods/Information Systems, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum of Agreement - VDACS/DED, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Coyote, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Endangered Species, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Fees - Feed, Seed, Fertilizer, Lime, Animal Remedies, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Motor Fuels Laboratory, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Pesticide Management - Marvin Lawson, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Pesticides, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Pesticides - Disposal, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Pesticides - Fees, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Pesticides - Recordkeeping, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Purple Loosestrife, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Seed Laboratory Fees, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Seed Testing Fees, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Sewage and Sludge Program, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Weights and Measures, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Dairy and Foods, Div. of - Mark D. Tubbs, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Dairy and Foods - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 32)
    - BST, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Food Inspection, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Fossomatic 90 Cell County, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Fresh fields, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Goat Milk, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Grade A Milk, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Virginia Academy of Science, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS, 1992-1993. (Box 32)
    - Accounts, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Administrative Process Act, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Affirmative Action Plan, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Africanized Honeybee, 1993. (Box 32)
    - African Trade Summit, 1993. (Box 32)
    - AG Week, 1993. (Box 32)
    - AG - A.M. - USDA, 1993. (Box 32)
    - State Agency Group Leaders, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Agenda - SMT meetings, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Agreement (loan) - Eastern Shore Marketing Cooperative/VDACS, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Agreement - VDACS/PCC, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Agreement - Agri Marketing SER/USDA/VDACS, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Agreement - USDA/VDACS Cooperative, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Agreement - VDACS/Virginia Cooperative Extension, 1993. (Box 32)
    - National Agriculture Day and Virginia Agriculutre Week, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Virginia Agricultural Development Authority - Annual Report, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Agricultural Economic Study, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Virginia Agricultural Statistics Service, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Air Pollution Control, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Virginia Alliance for the Public Service, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Commission on the Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program - Bi-annual Report, 1991-1992. (Box 32)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Apples, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Aquaculture Plan, Virginia, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Aquaculture Project - St. Paul's College, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Attorney General, 1993. (Box 32)
    - State Internal Auditor, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 32)
    - Audit - Auditor of Public Accounts (APA), 1993. (Box 32)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (APA), 1993. (Box 33)
    - Audits, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Awards - Quality Performance, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Awards Committee, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Beetle Pine Bark Infestation, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Senate Bills - 160 and 479, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Biotechnology Work Group, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Biotechnology - Registration of, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Blue Tongue, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Briefing to Secretary, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Capital Outlay Projects, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Trader Cattle, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Central Farmers Market, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Center for Public Service, 1993. (Box 33)
    - CMI Nominations, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia, 1993. (Box 33)
    - CHIPS - Hardwood experts, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Closings - Field Office, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Coastal Zone Management Act, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Virginia Code Commission, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC), 1993. (Box 33)
    - Commerce, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Commission on Local Government, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Commodity Boards, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Comptroller's Office, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Cotton, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Tobacco, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Tobacco Burley Warehouses, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Tours, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (VDOT), 1993. (Box 33)
    - USDA - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 33)
    - USDA, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Virginia's Finest - update, 1993. (Box 33)
    - VPI and SU, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Volunteerism, Office of, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Bottled Water, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Warrenton Laboratory, 1993. (Box 33)
    - State Water Control Board, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Worker Protection Standards, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Alternate Work Schedule, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 1993. (Box 33)
    - Board of Agriculture (VDACS), 1993. (Box 33)
    - Apple Board, Virginia State, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Aquaculture Advisory Board, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Cattle Industry Board, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Cattlemen's Association, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Board, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services Advisory Board, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Corn Board, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Corn Growers Association, National, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Dairymen's Association, Virginia State, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Farmers Market Board, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Farmers Markets, National Association of - Nutrition Program, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Feed Industry Advisory Committee, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Food and Drug Officials of the Southern States, Association of, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Horse Industry Advisory Board, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Marine Products Board, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) (#1), 1993. (Box 34)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA)(#2), 1993. (Box 34)
    - Nurserymen's Association, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Pesticide Control Board, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Poultry Federation, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA), 1993. (Box 34)
    - Soybean Association, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Southern United States Trade Association (SUSTA), 1993. (Box 34)
    - Toxic Substances Advisory Board, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Winegrowers Advisory Board, Virginia, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1993. (Box 34)
    - Memorandum of Understanding - VDACS/Dept. of Environmental Quality, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Memorandum of Understanding - VDACS/Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Memorandum of Understanding - VDACS/Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Memorandum of Understanding - VDACS/Virginia State University (Aquaculture Plan), 1993. (Box 35)
    - Memorandum of Understanding - VDACS/State Water Control Board, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Metrology Laboratory, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Mexico City Office, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Milk Commission, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Minor Crop - HR 967, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 35)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1993. (Box 35)
    - National Association of State Directors of Agriculture (NASDA) - Awards Program, 1993. (Box 35)
    - National Agriculture Marketing Association, 1993. (Box 35)
    - National Exhange Group, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Nutrition Labeling Education Act (NLEA), 1993. (Box 35)
    - Pay for Performance, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Pesticides - Diets of infants and children, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Pesticides Disposal Program, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Pesticides and Groundwater State Management Plan, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Policy - Family and Medical Leave, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Potatoes - White, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Prompt payment, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Purcell, John B., 1993. (Box 35)
    - Quality Improvement Plan, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Total Resource Conservation Planning, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Recyling, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Regional Meetings - VDACS, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Rental building, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Report to the Governor, 1991-1992. (Box 35)
    - Risk Management, Office of, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program (REAP), 1993. (Box 35)
    - Savings Bond Campaign, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Senators - Virginia, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Sole Source Authorization, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Southeeastern Virginia Farmers Market, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Southside Farmers Market, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Southern Governors Association - Summit, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Southside Virginia Produce Coop Board, 1993. (Box 35)
    - Southside Virginia Agricultural Association, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Southwest Virginia Farmers Market, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Soy Diesel, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Stage II Vapor Recovery Program, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Staunton-Augusta Farmers Market, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Strategic Planning, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Strategic Planning, 1992. (Box 36)
    - Agriculture Products Law Task Force, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Virginia Dealers in Agricultural Products, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Task Force on Cooperation with Land Grant Universities, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Task Force - Food Safety, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Task Force - Information Systems, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Task Force on International Studies and Global Trade, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Task Force on Livestock Disposal, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Nutrition Education Labeling Act, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Pesticide and Groundwater Task Force, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Task Force - Seasonal Agriculture Road Signs, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Taxation, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Constituent Correspondence and Suggested Responses, 1993. (Box 36)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council (meeting), 1993. (Box 36)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation (meeting), 1993. (Box 36)
    - SASDA (meeting), 1993. (Box 36)
    - Government Kiosk Exhibition (meeting), 1993. (Box 36)
    - Annual Valley Executive Economic Outlook Seminar, 1993. (Box 36)
    - House Agriculture Committee (meeting), 1993. (Box 36)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (meeting), 1993. (Box 36)
    - Mid-Atlantic Poultry Health Council (meeting), 1993. (Box 36)
    - VDACS Board Orientation, 1993. (Box 37)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (meeting), 1993. (Box 37)
    - Virginia Shellfish Growers Association (meeting), 1993. (Box 37)
    - Virginia Cooperative Extention 9th Annual Crop Field Day, 1993. (Box 37)
    - Virginia Agriculture Expo, 1993. (Box 37)
    - Aquaculture Advisory Board (meeting), 1993. (Box 37)
    - Virginia Wieghts and Measures Association (meeting), 1993. (Box 37)
    - Tobacco and the 103rd Congress, 1993. (Box 37)
    - VDACS/Commodity Board combined meeting, 1993. (Box 37)
    - Pesticide Control Board (meeting), 1993. (Box 37)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board (meeting), 1993. (Box 37)
    - Governor's Commission of Defense Conversion and Economic Adjustment, 1993. (Box 37)
    - Governor's Symposium on Virginia's Economic Outlook, 1992. (Box 37)
    - Internal Audits, 1993. (Box 37)
    - Regulatory Review, 1984-1985. (Box 38)
    - Regulatory Review, 1984-1985. (Box 39)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Legislation, 1989. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1992 Jan. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1991 July. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1991 May. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1991 Jan. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1990 Nov. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1990 Sept. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1990 Aug. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1990 July. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1990 May. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Correspondence, 1989-1991. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Pesticide Clean Day, 1990. (Box 40)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting with George Gilliam, 1990. (Box 41)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1990 May. (Box 41)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1990 Mar. (Box 41)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1989 Nov. (Box 41)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 1989 July. (Box 41)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Virginia Pesticide Control Act, 1989. (Box 41)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Retreat, 1989. (Box 41)
    - Pesticide Control Board - COE Pesticide Review Subcommittee, 1988-1989. (Box 41)
    - Turfgrass Marketing Plan, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Turkish Dairy Farmer Assistance, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Tobacco, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Transportation, Virginia Dept. of, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Tobacco Shed Distribution Program, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA), 1989 June. (Box 42)
    - Mid-Atlantic Poultry Health Council, 1989 Aug. (Box 42)
    - USDA - general information, 1989. (Box 42)
    - USDA - Revitalization Task Force, 1989. (Box 42)
    - US/USSR Trade and Economic Council, 1988. (Box 42)
    - US/Canadian Trade Agreement, 1988-1989. (Box 42)
    - First Strategy (VPI), 1989. (Box 42)
    - USDA - Packers and Stockyard Administration, 1987-1991. (Box 42)
    - VanaHo Soybeans/Mitsubishi, 1989. (Box 42)
    - VPI and SU, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Agri-Tech - VPI, 1989. (Box 42)
    - MOU - VDACS/VPI, 1981-1985. (Box 42)
    - VPI - Budege Initiatives, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Food Dealers, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Virginia State Feed Association, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Virginia Veterinary Medical Association, 1988-1991. (Box 42)
    - Virginia Association of Fairs, 1989. (Box 42)
    - Virginia Register of Regulation, 1989. (Box 42)
    - VA/MD College of Veterinary Medicine, 1989. (Box 43)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation, 1989. (Box 43)
    - Virginia District Export Council, 1989. (Box 43)
    - Forest Farmers Association, 1989-1990. (Box 43)
    - Petroleum Industry, 1989-1990. (Box 43)
    - Seed Industry Advisory Board, 1988. (Box 43)
    - Inter-American Development Bank - Roundtable Discusion, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Sustainable Agriculture Conference, 1990. (Box 43)
    - ASCS Conference, 1990. (Box 43)
    - National Simental Association, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Apple Marketing Conference, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Center for Innovative Technology, 1987. (Box 43)
    - Dr. Hockaday, 1987. (Box 43)
    - Senate Economic Development, 1988. (Box 43)
    - Seafood Inspection - Federal legislation, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Proposed Erosion Control regulsation, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Sunshine Mills, 1989. (Box 43)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1990 Dec. (Box 43)
    - Sunbelt Agricultural Expo, 1988-1990. (Box 43)
    - State Climatologist, 1984-1985. (Box 43)
    - Seed Certification - Legislation, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA) - general information, 1989-1990. (Box 43)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA) - Conference, 1990 June. (Box 43)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA) - Audit Committee, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Salmonella Enteritidis, 1990-1991. (Box 43)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1990-1991. (Box 43)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Society, 1990. (Box 43)
    - State Water Control Board, 1989-1990. (Box 43)
    - State Agency Auxiliary, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Soybean Referendum, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Sulfites - general information, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Showcase Virginia, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA) - Resolutions, 1990. (Box 43)
    - Toxic Substance Advisory Board, 1988-1991. (Box 43)
    - Targeted Export Assistance (TEA), 1989-1990. (Box 44)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority Agreement, 1988-1990. (Box 44)
    - Tobacco (general info), 1990-1991. (Box 44)
    - TC/Press International, 1989-1990. (Box 44)
    - CBS Tobacco Interview, 1990. (Box 44)
    - USDA - General info, 1990. (Box 44)
    - USDA - Soil and Conservation Service, 1989-1990. (Box 44)
    - USDA - Food and Agriculture Council (FAC), 1987-1991. (Box 44)
    - USDA - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Group (ASCS), 1987-1990. (Box 44)
    - USDA - Budget, 1990-1991. (Box 44)
    - Virginia Water Resouces Research Center, 1988-1991. (Box 44)
    - Virginia Vinyards Association, 1986-1990. (Box 44)
    - Virginia Turf Grass Conference, 1986-1989. (Box 44)
    - Virginia State Dairymen's Association, 1990-1991. (Box 44)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA), 1988-1991. (Box 45)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - USDA Potato Recom Meeting, 1988. (Box 45)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Agricultural Accord, 1988. (Box 45)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - States/Provinces Accord, 1988. (Box 45)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Canada/US Potato Group, 1987-1988. (Box 45)
    - State Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1989. (Box 45)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - States/Provinces Accord, 1990 May. (Box 46)
    - State Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1989 Feb. (Box 46)
    - State Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1988 Oct. (Box 46)
    - State Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1989 Sept. (Box 46)
    - State Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1989 Dec. (Box 46)
    - Evaluation, 1989. (Box 46)
    - Agency Service Agreement, 1982-1985. (Box 46)
    - Southern US Trade Association (SUSTA) Meeting 1991 Sept. (Box 46)
    - Southern US Trade Association (SUSTA) - Interstate Pest Control Compact - meeting, 1991 Sept. (Box 46)
    - BST - treated with, 1989-1990. (Box 47)
    - Bees (general info), 1988-1990. (Box 47)
    - CIT / Institute of Biotechnology, 1989. (Box 47)
    - Comptroller's Office, 1990-1991. (Box 47)
    - Council on the Environment - Quarterly meeting, 1991 Jan. (Box 47)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services, 1990. (Box 47)
    - Chesapeake Bay (general info #2), 1989-1991. (Box 47)
    - Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act, 1991. (Box 47)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services Board meeting, 1990 Dec. (Box 47)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services Board meeting, 1990 May. (Box 47)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services Board meeting, 1990 Feb. (Box 47)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services Board meeting, 1991 Feb. (Box 47)
    - CSX proposed rate increase, 1990. (Box 47)
    - Council on State Governments, 1990-1991. (Box 47)
    - Colorado potato beetle, 1990. (Box 47)
    - Conservation Council of Virginia, 1988-1990. (Box 47)
    - Coyote situation in Virginia, 1985-1989. (Box 47)
    - Carbofuran, 1988. (Box 47)
    - Census promotion campaign, 1990. (Box 47)
    - Delmarva Advisory Council, 1987-1988. (Box 47)
    - Drip Irrigation, 1987-1988. (Box 47)
    - Endangered Plant/Species Act, 1986-1990. (Box 47)
    - Endangered Species Protection Plan, 1989-1990. (Box 47)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1988-1990. (Box 48)
    - Export Development Advisory Committee, 1986-1987. (Box 48)
    - Agency Head meeting, 1990 Feb. (Box 48)
    - Agency Head meeting, 1990 May. (Box 48)
    - Agency Head retreat, 1990 Nov. (Box 48)
    - Economic Development, Secretary of (#3), 1990 Aug-1991 Jan. (Box 48)
    - Aquaculture, 1990-1991. (Box 48)
    - Aquaculture - meeting with Richard Burton, 1990 Dec. (Box 48)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Executive Committee meeting, 1991 Jan. (Box 48)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Guests and invitees, 1990. (Box 48)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Land Use, Natural Resources, and Environment, 1989. (Box 48)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Food Safety Survey, 1990. (Box 48)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Washington Office Reports, 1990. (Box 48)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Board of Directors meeting, 1991 Jn. (Box 48)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Conference, 1990 July. (Box 48)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Action policies, 1990. (Box 48)
    - NAMO meeting, 1990 July. (Box 48)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Food Show Task Force, 1990. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Action policies, 1990 Oct. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Mid-Year Conference, 1990 Mar. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - States/Provinces Accord, 1989-1990. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Policy Positions, 1990. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - FDA Task Force, 1990. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - DOI Task Force, 1990. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - USDA Task Force, 1990. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - EPA Task Force, 1989-1990. (Box 49)